

# **LILIANA PLATON**

UI/UX designer & Front-end developer

During my experience as an Office Administrator and CAD Technical Draftsman, I gained valuable experience in both administrative tasks and technical skills, as well as adaptability, a designoriented mindset, social skills, organizational abilities. These skills allow me to work efficiently in a team environment and maintain a keen focus on detail. Currently, I am focusing on web development. To gain experience and knowledge in this area, I have completed courses, built a portfolio, and I keep learning from resources like Udemy, CS50, Stack Overflow, MDN and Daily.dev.

# **CONTACT**

- (+40) 757 536 817
- Cluj-Napoca, Romania
- github.com/lilianaplaton
- in linkedin.com/in/lilianaplaton/
- → platonliliana1409@gmail.com
- portfoliolilianaplaton.netlify.app

# **PORTFOLIO**



## **SKILLS**

Figma | Photoshop | HTML5 | CSS3 | JavaScript | UI/UX design Learning React | Bootstrap | MS Office | Brand & Identity | GIT

Problem-solving. Research. Teamwork. Self-study. Communication. Curiosity. Creativity. Result-oriented and pragmatic. Empathy

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### Office Administrative

Ian 2020 - Feb 2023 | General Proex S.R.L., Cluj-Napoca

- Maintaining financial accountability, managing accounts;
- Brand & Identity (creating template designs for Gmail signature, agenda, documents, technical memory projects, bags, tags, and badges);
- Preparing and redacting documents and technical memory projects;
- Manage phone calls, correspondence, going on meetings/delegations;
- Order and maintain inventory of office supplies and equipment;
- Organizing and maintaining records, files, and databases;
- Operating office equipment (printer/scanner/plotter).

#### **CAD Technical Draftsman**

2017 - 2019 | Visionarh Dessin S.R.L., Cluj-Napoca

- Drafting drawings based on sketches
- Rendering of buildings/facades in the 3D Studio Max program
- Detailing the models (execution drawings)
- Checking graphic documentation
- Elaboration of drawings and presentation in space
- Rectification of plan/construction in photoshop

#### CERTIFICATIONS

Certificate | DECIDFR • Making websites and applications for www Sept 2021 - Feb 2022 | Postgraduate training program, UTCN

• It is a course for those who want to learn/create responsive websites using technologies such as HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, AJAX, and PHP.

Certificate in AutoCAD, Faculty of Machine Building

May 20 | Technical University of Cluj-Napoca

## **VOLUNTEER**

# OSSIMM, Technical University of Cluj-Napoca

2015 - 2016 | Organization of Students from Faculty of Materials and Environmental Engineering

#### **EDUCATION**

#### Technical University of Cluj-Napoca

2017 - 2019 | Master's degree: Faculty of Civil Engineering

• Engineering of Special Technologies in Construction

### Technical University of Cluj-Napoca

2013 - 2017 | Bachelor's degree: Faculty of Materials and Environmental Engineering

Engineering and Environmental Protection in Industry

#### High School "Miron Cristea" Subcetate

2009 - 2013 | Mathematics and Informatics